Guide to the Veteran Feminists of America Records, 1972-2017 RL.01331
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2009-0131), 2001-2008; 2 boxes
  - Administrative files, 2002-2006
    - Membership (Box 21)
    - Finances (Box 21)
    - Committees (Box 21)
    - Correspondence (Box 21)
  - Events and program files (Box 21)
  - Events and program files (Box 22)
    - Helen Reddy, 2006 (Box 22)
    - Barnard College, 2001 (Box 22)
    - Title VII conference, 2004 (Box 22)
    - Title IX conference, 2002 (Box 22)
    - Louisiana event, 2001 (Box 22)
  - Publicity and publications (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous files (Box 22)
  - Salute to Feminist Lawyers event, June 2008 (Box 23)
    - Advisory Committee
      - Correspondence with advisors, 2007-2008 (Box 23)
      - Advisory Committee addresses (Box 23)
    - Law event
      - Database (includes CD), 2007 (Box 23)
      - Invitation (Box 23)
      - Guests (Box 23)
    - Honorees
      - Correspondence with honorees, 2008 (Box 23)
      - Honorees originals, 2007-2008 (Box 23)
      - Honorees current list, 2008 (Box 23)
      - Honorees addresses (Box 23)
      - Pauli Murray (Box 23)
    - Ruth Bader Ginsburg
      - Tributes (Box 23)
      - Correspondence (Box 23)
      - Ginsburg biography (Box 23)
    - Printed program
      - Vera Glaser program (Box 23)
      - Biographies (Box 23)
      - Historic (Box 23)
      - Legal advocacy groups (Box 23)
      - Tobias introduction (Box 23)
      - In memorium (Box 23)
      - Layout (Box 23)
      - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Day program
      - Current legal issues (Box 23)
      - Panel 1: Changing the Law (Box 23)
    - Event
      - Videographer (Box 23)
      - VFA website (Box 23)
      - Poster (Box 23)
      - Registration form (Box 23)
      - Registrants (Box 23)
      - Budget (Box 23)
      - Handouts (possible) (Box 23)
      - Attendees (Box 23)
      - Press release (Box 23)
      - Donors (Box 23)
      - Booklets (Box 23)
      - VFA Salutes Feminist Lawyers tote bag (Box 23)
- Accession (2010-0097), 2005-2010, 1 box
  The addition (2010-0097) (300 items; 0.6 lin. ft., dated 2005-2010) includes miscellaneous newsletters, dated 2005-2008; board meeting minutes from 2007; event and program files from a 2009 Pompano Beach, FL awards gala and a Dallas conference entitled The Gender Agenda: Beyond Borders, held March 2010. The Dallas event files include copies of materials on 22 honorees, as well as the program text and other promotional materials. Other topics in this accession include website initiatives and the Feminists Who Changed America book launch.
  - Feminists Who Changed America book launch, 2006 (Box 24)
  - Newsletters and Board Meeting minutes, 2005-2008 (Box 24)
  - Feminists of the Month website feature, 2009-2010 (Box 24)
  - Pompano Beach, Florida event, April 2009 (Box 24)
  - The Gender Agenda: Beyond Borders conference, Dallas, March 2010
    - Planning materials (Box 24)
    - Promotional materials (Box 24)
    - Program text (Box 24)
    - Copies of materials on 22 honorees (Box 24)
  - Tote bag from A Salute to Feminist Lawyers event, 2008 (Box 24)
- Accession (2010-0128), 2009-2010, 1 box
  The addition (2010-0128) (150 items; 0.6 lin. ft., dated 2009-2010) includes materials submitted by honorees at the The Gender Agenda: Beyond Borders conference held by the VFA in Dallas. Materials include information forms, resumes, essays, and other miscellaneous biographies.
  - The Gender Agenda: Beyond Borders information forms and supplemental materials, 2009-2010, 5 folders (Box 25)
- Accession (2012-0083), 2006, 2009, 1 folder
  The addition (2012-0083) (4 items; 0.1 lin. ft., dated 2006, 2009) includes a program from the Tribute to Helen Reddy event (2006) and two copies of an associated commerically-available music compact disc by Sandy Rapp; along with the souvenir program from the VFA salute to feminist lawyers (2009).
  - Tribute to Helen Reddy and salute to feminist lawyers programs, two compact discs, 2006, 2009, 1 folder (Box 25)
- Accession (2015-0069), 1971-2014, 3 boxes
  Scope and Contents
  The addition (2015-0069) (1800 items; 2.0 lin. ft., dated 1971-2014) consists of event information, program and administrative files relating to the activities of the Veteran Feminists of America. Special media formats include DVDs of event programming.
  - Event programs, 2005-2012 (Box 26)
  - Rollins 2011 (Box 26)
  - VFA Board Meeting (Box 26)
  - VFA Friedan NY, 2011 (Box 26)
  - Feminists Who Changed America Book Release, 2007 (Box 26)
  - Connecticut, 2005 (Box 26)
  - VFA Lawyers, 2008-2009 (Box 26)
  - Pompano Beach, 2009 (Box 26)
  - Tuscon Events, 2006 (Box 26)
  - Biography Solicitations (Box 26)
  - President's Report, 2012 (Box 26)
  - VFA Current, 2012 (Box 26)
  - VFA Website Revisions, 2012 (Box 26)
  - VFa Legacy Collection (Box 26)
  - Alverno Magazine, Spring 2012 (Box 26)
  - Milwaukee VFA, 2012 (Box 26)
  - Data, n.d. (Box 26)
  - Millett Event, 2012 (Box 26)
  - Fundraiser Letters, 2010 (Box 26)
  - Nominations to Board/Officers (Box 26)
  - Birthday Party, 2013 (Box 26)
  - VFA Solicitation 2010-2013 (Box 26)
  - VFA, 2013 (Box 27)
  - VFA Meeting, 2012 (Box 27)
  - VFA Board, 2011 (Box 27)
  - Dallas Meeting Resolutions, 2010-2011 (Box 27)
  - VFA Application, 2010-2011 (Box 27)
  - VFA Orlando Event, 2010-2011 (Box 27)
  - VFA Rollins College, 2010-2011 (Box 27)
  - Board Meeting, n.d. (Box 27)
  - DVD information, including CD, 1993-2004 (Box 27)
  - Feminists Who Changed America flyer, n.d. (Box 27)
  - FWCA flyer, n.d. (Box 27)
  - NOW Founders, 2010 (Box 27)
  - Photos, n.d. (Box 27)
  - VFA Newsletters, 1992-2004 (Box 27)
  - Historic Photos, n.d. (Box 27)
  - Tobias, 2003-2009 (Box 27)
  - VFA History, 2004-2007 (Box 27)
  - Women's Studies, 1971-2000 (Box 27)
  - Women's Liberation Movement 30th Anniversary Event, 1997 (Box 27)
  - Renewal Incorporation, 2014 (Box 28)
  - Ms. Magazine, 2013 (Box 28)
  - Appeals, 2013-2014 (Box 28)
  - VFA LA Liability (Box 28)
  - Copy Originals, n.d. (Box 28)
  - Friedan Piece, 2012 (Box 28)
  - DVD Wrap, 2006-2013 (Box 27)
  - Duke Agreement, 2013 (Box 28)
  - VFA History, 2013 (Box 28)
  - Alverno Report (Box 28)
  - Wendy Davis, 2006-2013 (Box 28)
  - Board Meeting, n.d. (Box 28)
  - Invitation, 2013 (Box 28)
  - Honorees, 2013 (Box 28)
  - Wired, n.d. (Box 28)
  - LA Event, 2013 (Box 28)
  - Labor and the Women's Movement Event, 2014; 5 DVDs (Box 28)
  - Kate Millett Festival 2012, 2 DVDs +CD, 3 folders (Box 28)
- Accession (2017-0058), 2002-2017
  - Conference Programs, 2004-2005 (Box 29)
  - Conference Programs, 2014-2017 (Box 29)
  - Conference Programs and DVDs, 2009-2014 (Box 29)
  - Annual Board Meeting Minutes, 2002-2016 (Box 29)
- Accession (2017-0139), 1992-2017
  - Board and Officers, 2010-2017 (Box 30)
  - Duke Program Book, 2017 (Box 30)
  - DVD, Wrap Agreement, 2007-2008 (Box 30)
  - LA Event, 2013 (Box 30)
  - President Report, 2016 (Box 30)
  - VFA: A History, 2013-2017 (Box 30)
  - VFA Planning and Projects, 1992-2015 (Box 30)
  - VFA Proposal: Documenting Feminist Activism, 2015 (Box 30)